<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>religious on ht.xyz</title>
    <link>/tags/religious/</link>
    <description>Recent content in religious on ht.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/religious/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 12 - PutanaVadh</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_12/</guid>
      <description>Recap The eighth child of Devaki was saved by divine intervention. He is now the child of Yashoda and Nandraj from Gokul village.
Putana  Vidhaata! Bhaagya! Likh!
 Synopsis Realizing that the eighth child is a girl and not a boy, Kansa tries to kill her, but the child flies away from his hand and screams from the sky that his destroyer is already born. Kansa sets on the search to find the real eighth child of Devaki while Gokul celebrates the birth of Krishna.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 11 - The Birth of Shri Krishna</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_11/</guid>
      <description>Recap Kansa terrorizes Mathura, and is prophesied to be killed by the eighth son of his own sister. He imprisons them so that he can kill her children right when they&amp;rsquo;re born.
Divine birth  Meri aur yoon na dekho devaki, dekhna hai to uss brahma ki aur dekho. Jisne tumhari kokh ko meri aur uski ranbhoomi me badal diya hai.
 Synopsis Kansa kills six of Devaki&amp;rsquo;s children one by one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 10 - The prophecy</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_10/</guid>
      <description>Recap Previously we saw the birth of the main players in this story, the Pandavs and Kauravs. Now we move on to the exploits of everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite little god, Shree Krishna.
The Prophecy  Meri ladai to Brahma se hai
 Synopsis Taking a break from Hastinapur and the kuru vansh, we are introduced to Kansa, the prince of Mathura as he overthrows his father and takes over the royal throne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 9 - Dhritrashtra is king</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_09/</guid>
      <description>Recap Last we saw Pandu in the woods, enjoying a well deserved vacation with his queens. His wives by his side, things look good for him. Meanwhile, Dhritrashtra seems to be ready to take over the throne as king himself.
The blind king  Hatya tum kar nahi sakte, aur durghatna pe tumhara vash nahi.
 Synopsis Satyavati calls for Pandu&amp;rsquo;s return to the royal court. Before returning, Madri asks Pandu to hunt a tiger for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 8 - Madri</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_08/</guid>
      <description>Recap We left the court of Hastinapur under the able leadership of Pandu when we last met. He married Kunti, and his blind brother Dhritrashtra was married to Gandhari. We also got to see the birth of Karn, the gifted son from Surya Dev to Kunti, who she had to abandon in the river.
Madri  Aap Chandravanshi hai aryaputra, katore me padi chandrama ki chhaya ko chandrama samaj lena aapko shobha nahi deta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 7 - The birth of Karn</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_07/</guid>
      <description>Recap Last we saw the beginnings of what would become the war between Kauravas and Pandavs, and how the whole thing came to be. We saw Dhritrashtra give away his throne to his younger brother Pandu on Vidur&amp;rsquo;s suggestion.
The birth of Karn  Apna daan apni maa se aarambh karo daanveer Karn, apni maa ko kshama kar do.
 Synopsis In this episode, Bhishma arranges the marriage of the blind son Dhritrashtra with the princess of Gandhar, Gandhari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 6 - The birth of Pandu, Dhritrashtra and Vidur</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_06/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: I have added a commenting functionality to the site, it is for mail-in comments so it may or may not be up your lane. Try it if you feel like!
After feedback from the exactly three people that read this website, I have discovered that the series seems like a story retelling and not a discussion. So after this one, all the episdode discussions that are posted on this site will have three sections, viz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 5 - Amba, Ambika, Ambalika</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_05/</guid>
      <description>Recap Now that the reign of Shantanu is over, we move on to bigger things. Things that will set in motion one of the biggest wars to take place in India. Bhishma, now the protector of the princes Chitrangad and Vichitravir as well as the kingdom, now holds the court by proxy.
Amba, Ambika, Ambalika  Ghatnaao aur durghatnaao ke paas koi ichchhashakti nahi hoti
 I feel like some long unnecessary parts of the story are skipped, and rightly so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 4 - Ichchha Mrityu</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_04/</guid>
      <description>Recap After a two weeks of inactivity, here I am again. Two weeks ago we saw how Devvrat was ready to give up worldly pleasures just so his father can stay happy and in turn, the kingdom of Hastinapur can prosper. His vow of celibacy was called Bhishma or terrible. Moving on let&amp;rsquo;s see how Shantanu tries to justify his son taking up celibacy for his father.
Ichchha Mrityu  &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;shanti aur ashanti ke daurahe par khada ye Shantanu tumhe ye vardaan deta hai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 3 - The Vow (Bhishma Pratigya)</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_03/</guid>
      <description>Recap Back to the story after a very uneventful episode, this is a turning point in the story of Devvrat and Shantanu, and on a larger scale the kingdom of Hastinapur. We saw Ganga tell Shantanu why she did what she did (infanticide), which was merciful in a way. Shantanu waits for about 16 years for his son to get his training and come back, prepped to be heir in the democratic kingdom of Hastinapur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 2 - Ganga reveals the Truth</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_02/</guid>
      <description>Recap In the previous episode, we had a brief look at the life of King Shantanu, and his river/wife/queen Ganga. We saw her kill their newborn babies one after another, while Shantanu watched helplessly. While the reason is unknown, we can imagine that the heartless killings must have some substance to them. Why else would a mother kill seven of her newborns? In this episode we will see Shantanu choose between his love for his wife and his love for his children that don&amp;rsquo;t get to see a day of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 1, part 1 - The story of king Bharat</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_01/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the first of the many reviews I will be posting of the much loved Mahabharat television series that aired on DD National when I did not even exist.
I will try to post here weekly, and before each discussion, we will have a recap of what went on last time in this epic story and how things are looking for our characters in this game of dharma, karma, and glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 1, part 2 - The wedding of Shantanu</title>
      <link>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_01p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahabharat/mahabharat_episode_01p2/</guid>
      <description>Recap Last we saw king Bharat establish a new trend of choosing the ruler by merit and not by right of birth. Many years have passed since then and now we look at another king of Hastinapur, Shantanu.
The wedding of Shantanu  To ek vachan dijiye.
  Aaj se mere saare vachan tumhare
 Shantanu, who is out to hunt deer (because that&amp;rsquo;s what kings do in their free time) spots a beautiful lady come out of a river.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from Hanumanji</title>
      <link>/posts/joy_of_hanuman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/joy_of_hanuman/</guid>
      <description>Shri Hanuman is the epitome of selfless service, courage, hope and strength. He is, and should be an inspiration to us all in more that one ways. Even for those who don&amp;rsquo;t believe in him, his story is one with valuable life lessons.
Unfathomable innocence has always been a defining character of Shri Hanuman, according to me. Since he was a child, his childish innocent actions never let the devotee/reader think that they&amp;rsquo;re reading/thinking about a literal god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and its reasons</title>
      <link>/posts/religion_and_people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/religion_and_people/</guid>
      <description>I was an atheist in the past. It was less because of my personal beliefs and more because all the cool kids did it, but other than that, my religion was liberal in that matter. It allowed us to do as we wish, to follow who we want.
Not knowing what it was to have someone to look to for support, someone who you have never met irl and yet they are the strongest power you know, is something that I only realized after I got out of the atheist phase.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
