<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on ht.xyz</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on ht.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>tidytilde, A script to make your $HOME clean and tidy.</title>
      <link>/projects/tidytilde/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/tidytilde/</guid>
      <description>tidytilde, a script to make your $HOME clean and tidy. Sometimes your $HOME directory gets too cluttered with .dotfiles and it just looks very unclean. Fortunately the archwiki has a nice article on how to make it tidy. tidytilde automates many of the dotfiles listed there, and since it is a long list, it might be a while before all the files are implemented. You just need to run the script and it will move the files to the necessary location and create a file called tidytilde_commands in your $HOME directory which will contain all the environment variables and aliases that need to be set at startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time In TTY, a CLI timetracking script </title>
      <link>/projects/ti-tty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/ti-tty/</guid>
      <description>Ti-tty a command line time tracking shell script This is a time tracking shell script, used to track time for ongoing projects or some other task that needs time tracking. It uses unix timestamp and the date utility that comes with most unix-like operating systems. It is lightweight, and does one thing well, track time. It is similar to Timewarrior but the difference is in the implementation, as in timewarrior is too complex for my use case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo htxyz, a hugo theme</title>
      <link>/projects/hugo-htxyz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/hugo-htxyz/</guid>
      <description>Hugo-htxyz [Hugo](gohugo.io) is one of the most popular open-source static site generators. With its amazing speed and flexibility, Hugo makes building websites fun again.  Hugo has multiple themes that can be used to generate static sites. The sites can be minimal or pretty much full fledged, depending on the templates and the build time is FAST. Since I have been using a hugo for a while, I thought I should make my own theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ul.dl, the no-bullshit file hosting service</title>
      <link>/projects/uldl_file_sharing_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/uldl_file_sharing_service/</guid>
      <description>ul.dl, the no-bullshit file hosting service You might have heard of 0x0, the no-bullshit file hosting service. It is a service for quickly sharing files right from your command line without having to point or click anywhere. What you do is, you send a POST request to the site with the file and the site will respond with a url that has the raw content of that file.
For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>comments.js, a lightweight serverless commenting engine</title>
      <link>/projects/commenting_engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/commenting_engine/</guid>
      <description>How I made my own commenting engine Well, before you go on, you might be wondering, what is a commenting engine? A commenting engine is a piece of code that handles comments on a website or app and the likes. On this website, before this point, there was no option for comments. After that I tried messing with some commenting engines such as Disqus and Staticman and many more. My core issue with most of these was that either they were hosted by third party, or they needed some sort of hosting by the site owner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
