<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ht.xyz</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ht.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things that I find worth sharing</title>
      <link>/posts/interesting_links/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/interesting_links/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of links that I keep and update regularly. It might be of use to you.
Learning Resources  https://learnxinyminutes.com/ |	what the name suggests https://www.raspberrypi.org/forums/viewtopic.php?t=251645 | guide to install KODI on rpi https://shellscript.sh | Shell scripting guide https://tldp.org/LDP/abs/html/ | Shell scripting guide http://www.eskimo.com/~scs/cclass/cclass.html | C Programming Guide https://quadpoint.org/articles/irssi/ | Guide to using irssi https://tldp.org/ | The Linux Documentation project, lots of html style guides https://www.cheatsheet.wtf/ | cheatsheet for Linux related stuff https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Development] ul.dl, the no-bullshit file hosting service</title>
      <link>/posts/uldl_file_sharing_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/uldl_file_sharing_service/</guid>
      <description>ul.dl, the no-bullshit file hosting service You might have heard of 0x0, the no-bullshit file hosting service. It is a service for quickly sharing files right from your command line without having to point or click anywhere. What you do is, you send a POST request to the site with the file and the site will respond with a url that has the raw content of that file.
For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Development] Setting up Cloudflare Argo Tunnel on Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>/posts/argo_tunnel_on_pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/argo_tunnel_on_pi/</guid>
      <description>Setting up Cloudflare Argo Tunnel on my Raspberry Pi This is a way to set up cloudflare argo tunnel on your Raspberry Pi to host your own webserver without port forwarding.
KEEP IN MIND THAT THIS IS NOT RECOMMENDED FOR SENSITIVE DATA AS IT WILL BE PASSING THROUGH CLOUDFLARE SERVERS. What is argo tunnel? It is a tunneling service provided by Cloudflare to help users tunnel connections to their servers via the cloudflare network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Development] My own commenting engine!</title>
      <link>/posts/commenting_engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/commenting_engine/</guid>
      <description>Update: I don&amp;rsquo;t use this anymore because frankly it is kind of hacky. I hope people might find better use for this.
How I made my own commenting engine Well, before you go on, you might be wondering, what is a commenting engine? A commenting engine is a piece of code that handles comments on a website or app and the likes. On this website, before this point, there was no option for comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from Hanumanji</title>
      <link>/posts/joy_of_hanuman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/joy_of_hanuman/</guid>
      <description>Shri Hanuman is the epitome of selfless service, courage, hope and strength. He is, and should be an inspiration to us all in more that one ways. Even for those who don&amp;rsquo;t believe in him, his story is one with valuable life lessons.
Unfathomable innocence has always been a defining character of Shri Hanuman, according to me. Since he was a child, his childish innocent actions never let the devotee/reader think that they&amp;rsquo;re reading/thinking about a literal god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[FIX] ELan touchpad stops working at boot</title>
      <link>/posts/touchpadrestart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/touchpadrestart/</guid>
      <description>There was this issue that I faced in my system (HP Pavilion Gaming 15 Laptop) in which the touchpad (ElanTech) would stop working when the laptop booted, the fix to which was to move my finger on the touchpad when the system was booting up. Doing this every time was not convenient, so it took me a while, but this is what I did.
Create a script, called touchpadrestart.sh and put the below code in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and its reasons</title>
      <link>/posts/religion_and_people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/religion_and_people/</guid>
      <description>I was an atheist in the past. It was less because of my personal beliefs and more because all the cool kids did it, but other than that, my religion was liberal in that matter. It allowed us to do as we wish, to follow who we want.
Not knowing what it was to have someone to look to for support, someone who you have never met irl and yet they are the strongest power you know, is something that I only realized after I got out of the atheist phase.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
