<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on ht.xyz</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on ht.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright> Hitarth Thummar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 3 - The Vow (Bhishma Pratigya)</title>
      <link>/posts/mahabharat_episode_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mahabharat_episode_3/</guid>
      <description>Recap Back to the story after a very uneventful episode, this is a turning point in the story of Devvrat and Shantanu, and on a larger scale the kingdom of Hastinapur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 2 - Ganga reveals the Truth</title>
      <link>/posts/mahabharat_episode_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mahabharat_episode_2/</guid>
      <description>Recap In the previous episode, we had a brief look at the life of King Shantanu, and his river/wife/queen Ganga. We saw her kill their newborn babies one after another, while Shantanu watched helplessly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 1, part 1 - The story of king Bharat</title>
      <link>/posts/mahabharat_episode_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mahabharat_episode_1/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the first of the many reviews I will be posting of the much loved Mahabharat television series that aired on DD National when I did not even exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahabharat - Episode 1, part 2 - The wedding of Shantanu</title>
      <link>/posts/mahabharat_episode_1p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mahabharat_episode_1p2/</guid>
      <description>Recap Last we saw king Bharat establish a new trend of choosing the ruler by merit and not by right of birth. Many years have passed since then and now we look at another king of Hastinapur, Shantanu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from Hanumanji</title>
      <link>/posts/joy_of_hanuman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/joy_of_hanuman/</guid>
      <description>Shri Hanuman is the epitome of selfless service, courage, hope and strength. He is, and should be an inspiration to us all in more that one ways. Even for those who don&amp;rsquo;t believe in him, his story is one with valuable life lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of a tree</title>
      <link>/posts/death_of_a_tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/death_of_a_tree/</guid>
      <description>When a tree dies
The wayward souls lose their shade.
Their shade is no more, Neither is the cold whistling of the wind which moves the leaves- A lullaby to listening ears</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mangoes in cardboard boxes</title>
      <link>/posts/mangoes_in_cardboard_boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mangoes_in_cardboard_boxes/</guid>
      <description>like alcohol in the stone pits hailed, wanted, but lonely. In limbo, unhinged from reality thinking about the skies, while baffled by morality.
I scoured the universe, in search of salvation while my god&amp;rsquo;s abode was in my soul&amp;rsquo;s foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>अंतर</title>
      <link>/posts/antar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/antar/</guid>
      <description>उदासी तुझमें है, तनहाई मेरे भी अंदर है, लोग वही है, समय बस अलग है। काल चक्र का कोई जादू सा मंतर है। कैसे बताऊं मै? कोई अदृश्य अक्षर है। बातें वही है, बस शब्दों में कुछ अंतर है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[FIX] ELan touchpad stops working at boot</title>
      <link>/posts/touchpadrestart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/touchpadrestart/</guid>
      <description>There was this issue that I faced in my system (HP Pavilion Gaming 15 Laptop) in which the touchpad (ElanTech) would stop working when the laptop booted, the fix to which was to move my finger on the touchpad when the system was booting up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Fry</title>
      <link>/posts/smallfry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/smallfry/</guid>
      <description>Universes die. Then what am I? A measly human, a small fry.
Life gives and life takes. And the rest of it, death rakes. Civilizations are devoured, Myths forgotten, Languages are lost In the jaws of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and its reasons</title>
      <link>/posts/religion_and_people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/religion_and_people/</guid>
      <description>I was an atheist in the past. It was less because of my personal beliefs and more because all the cool kids did it, but other than that, my religion was liberal in that matter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
