<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poems on ht.xyz</title>
    <link>/poems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Poems on ht.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/poems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add.noise</title>
      <link>/poems/old/add.noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/add.noise/</guid>
      <description>Decibels upon decibels of your absence uncalled for. Blind ears and deaf eyes of leaders I vote for. Spread fear and slap lies on my face like some whore What you say is not what you do What you say is not true And I&amp;rsquo;m not a puppet To be controlled by your singing strings So please, Listen to me. Stop your vendetta and this societal violence And add noise To your deafening silence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>at_night</title>
      <link>/poems/old/at_night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/at_night/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s beautiful out here at night. You should come see it sometime.
The roads are empty, Streetlights burn bright The cold seeps through your heart And yet the fire inside fights.
Problems are a matter of tomorrow. This is your time to live Forget your sorrows At least until this time you borrowed Runs out, and before you know it, It&amp;rsquo;s over. Guns out Time to fight that war again, Time to be reborn again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>convert</title>
      <link>/poems/old/convert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/convert/</guid>
      <description>like alcohol in the stone pits hailed, wanted, but lonely. In limbo, unhinged from reality thinking about the skies, while baffled by morality.
I scoured the universe, in search of salvation while my god&amp;rsquo;s abode was in my soul&amp;rsquo;s foundation.
like mangoes in cardboard boxes sweet, free from paradoxes In heaven, hinged to reality thinking about the world unbothered by mortality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do_cavemen_dream</title>
      <link>/poems/old/do_cavemen_dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/do_cavemen_dream/</guid>
      <description>Do cavemen dream of stormy skies, spread far and wide? Do they cower in fear of what lies within? Or hope that its all a fever dream, and hide their heads in their mother’s laps, peeking between their fingergaps.
Do cavemen dream of cheery weather? And Singing birds with flashy feathers? Clear skies, fluffy clouds where they could shout their truth aloud. Or do they live just like us? In fear of what we must become, to live out till seventy one and lose the will to have some fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drive</title>
      <link>/poems/old/drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/drive/</guid>
      <description>On lonely nights I think of you and take a drive down degenerate lane. The tar becomes your skin, solid, but soothing. Your eyes are the stars watching me from afar. While sex appeal drips drowsily from your lips on my windshield, just for me to wipe it off. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how long I drive, your threads keep unraveling strand after strand covering me with your scent until there&amp;rsquo;s no air left for me to breathe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drowning</title>
      <link>/poems/old/drowning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/drowning/</guid>
      <description>I dream to see land And flying seagulls on the shore This sea now sickens me No more I want to explore.
Now I&amp;rsquo;m stuck in it No ship to sail in The sun has sucked me dry No tears left, yet I keep wailing.
They romanticize the ocean Talk about exploring the unexplored But in looking at the sun The dark waters they ignore
Yes, hope is an ocean With water infinite But what&amp;rsquo;s the point of it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>H</title>
      <link>/poems/old/h/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/h/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not what I used to be anymore, Hiding behind tasteless humor. I don&amp;rsquo;t write I haven&amp;rsquo;t read a book in forever My life is a slimy mix Of caffeine, nicotine and THC All day I roam the streets I can&amp;rsquo;t sleep at nights I keep messing with the bed sheets Fuck it! I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy from tommorow I keep lying to myself Can&amp;rsquo;t hide behind those lies anymore. My notes app is a collection of empty notes Half written poems Which I don&amp;rsquo;t intend to finish Even this poem is shit I know But I needed to let it out Let the world know I&amp;rsquo;m not what I used to be anymore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>heaven</title>
      <link>/poems/old/heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/heaven/</guid>
      <description>I miss being a kid my heart under a lid, covered. no ache, and no lovers, no secrets to uncover. I missed being naive at least. between shadows and mist, I played not a moment in dismay. and then my head I laid, in heaven my mother&amp;rsquo;s lap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>/poems/old/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/history/</guid>
      <description>A text here A picture there Crumpled up into moments we shared.
I would say fuck you But I have tested my luck too And kept failing to obscure you.
We shared a history With an emphasis on the D I&amp;rsquo;m not glued to you anymore, I&amp;rsquo;m free.
Consolations of being each other&amp;rsquo;s walls You dug your way in my heart&amp;rsquo;s halls But unlike you, your lies were tall.
We&amp;rsquo;re done now, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen you through I say we shared a history, like it&amp;rsquo;s true But it seems like only I shared it with you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June</title>
      <link>/poems/june/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/june/</guid>
      <description>Of cloudy skies and petrichor, Thirty days an eternity. &amp;lsquo;twas the best month of them all. Of cloudy skies and petrichor, and bruised ribs and broken bones The sun was all that we could see. Of cloudy skies and petrichor, Thirty days an eternity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kanye</title>
      <link>/poems/old/kanye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/kanye/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t help but hear The soundtrack to my self destruction pulling me in with tremendous suction. I can&amp;rsquo;t help but hear The very voice of my deepest fears Rapping over some dope production. I can&amp;rsquo;t help but hear The soundtrack to my self destruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maa</title>
      <link>/poems/old/maa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/maa/</guid>
      <description>जो कुछ छिपा है सीने में, तू कैसे वो सब जानती है मेरी हसी के पीछे का ग़म कैसे तू पहचानती है?
शब्द कम पड़ जाते है तेरे एहसान गिनाने में आज एक दिन वो कर पाएगा चंद अफसाने गाने से?
फिर भी आज बैठकर कुछ कोशिश मै कर रहा हूं, कुछ कर दिखाऊं उससे पहले तुझे खोने से मै डर रहा हूं।
 H.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mere_traveller</title>
      <link>/poems/old/mere_traveller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/mere_traveller/</guid>
      <description>I am but a mere Traveller On a dusty winding road, With only a box of feelings And my pet toad. I met many people, many strangers, Many foes. But only some of them deserve their roles, In my trampled, stampled life. This road might fork one day Or go on forever, A dead end might come anytime, If I don&amp;rsquo;t get clever. I am but a mere Traveller, On this dusty, winding road ; And I still wish the journey would get lively Like my little pet toad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not_quite_there</title>
      <link>/poems/old/not_quite_there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/not_quite_there/</guid>
      <description>I wanted you to know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been wondering lately. If I ever lose you, Who&amp;rsquo;s going to berate me?
Who&amp;rsquo;s going to mock me, For not being social? For always being disappointing, For never being hopeful.
I know I try too hard, It&amp;rsquo;s because you&amp;rsquo;re my idol Even though you&amp;rsquo;re broken Barely hanging on, suicidal.
I try to find the good in you, yet to see it somewhere. But I fear that one rainy morning, You won&amp;rsquo;t be there, to not be there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>/poems/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/now/</guid>
      <description>I see light-headed hipsters high on Sensationalized trends Performing ecstatical stunts Fueled by purposeless strength. Halt the boat, for the time is now To burn the place down Look around, You&amp;rsquo;ll see pretentious pussies Pasting pointless posts on Pedantic positivity and preposterous presumptions For perverted pathetic, Pussies. Consumed by the love for Quirks and bizzare things Things that are never real, never been. Eyes like sacks of sand hanging heavy On faces who&amp;rsquo;ve seen some shit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretense</title>
      <link>/poems/old/pretense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/pretense/</guid>
      <description>This life that i lead figured out, but really not My face is winning this race, Although my face lies a lot.
Lies, thrown right on your face, Sweet vanilla cake frosting And yet in my sincerest thoughts These lies are pretty exhausting
You swarm right in my home suck on my honey-coated lies and you&amp;rsquo;ll keep barging in Until you&amp;rsquo;ve sucked me dry.
Brainwashed bees still bust in my halls Of tense, morbid thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rehab</title>
      <link>/poems/old/rehab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/rehab/</guid>
      <description>This turmoil I feel, Is it made up or is it real?
I hear things, Faint ringing of a lost song Eternally plagued By a past long gone.
I want to take on the path less taken. But what if it&amp;rsquo;s not? What if I&amp;rsquo;m mistaken?
Barely hanging on, I&amp;rsquo;m fighting this curse. but I find my solace in penning this verse.
Monotonous, malignant musings of a mediocre mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rhyme</title>
      <link>/poems/old/rhyme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/rhyme/</guid>
      <description>Two quick beats, miss a step then repeat. My heart does that when your touch it needs. I cry and I Plead, and I Beg on my knees, But all you do is laugh at me and lie and deceive
I hope that you talk and I could tell you What I need
But jokes and insults are all I recieve. Two quick beats miss a step Then repeat I wish I could Stop acting Like a little kid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seasons</title>
      <link>/poems/old/seasons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/seasons/</guid>
      <description>I passed through the biting winds of winter igniting fires of a furious summer broken dreams of burning leaves and the sweet sweet fruit of spring. winds of desperation biting my face. running limbless in this life&amp;rsquo;s race. failing, losing and cursing myself in the end, discovering new ways to pass through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side_mirror</title>
      <link>/poems/old/side_mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/side_mirror/</guid>
      <description>I love you, you loved me i&amp;rsquo;m riding alone, it&amp;rsquo;s just me Side mirror loose, adjust it Betrayel lane, injustice Your colored smoke, engulfs me I breathe it in, I&amp;rsquo;m set free You are a magic entity Your cheap tricks disgust me I&amp;rsquo;m smoking a cheap cigar No beerbongs and bentleys You act like the 80s A little coked up, a bit carefree I am a lonely masochist Inflict pain, I&amp;rsquo;ll love it The side mirror of my ride it was loose, you cracked it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacups</title>
      <link>/poems/teacups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/teacups/</guid>
      <description>We sit here Alone, broken Bashed into, forsaken. An eternity we have longed For the steam of kettle To turn into a song And the noisy waterfall of a fiery hot drink To Fill our leaking bases Before we go extinct. Instead, harsh rain fills us Every few months or so And we let it molest us We have nowhere to go But we will have our day We ignore what the commode And the broken cars say After all they&amp;rsquo;re trash Their purpose long fulfilled And we&amp;rsquo;re broken teacups in a junkyard Waiting to be filled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violence</title>
      <link>/poems/old/violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/violence/</guid>
      <description>Gunships crash And burn into nothingness, Following this ritual eternally Until the heavenly fires Burn it all. And what&amp;rsquo;s left will be Nothing at all.
Warriors clash And Strike their blades blunt, Fighting till their last breath Until their commander Says stop. And the war that began Forever stays stalled.
Violence stays Forever in my heart. Slurping my soul, skulking about. And No matter how hard I try To wrench it out It won&amp;rsquo;t leave my soul Until I battle it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weather</title>
      <link>/poems/old/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/weather/</guid>
      <description>winds screaming out their lungs.
rain beating the fuck out of tar roads.
clouds, tinted with the shades of my heart,
hiding the sun as he cowers behind.
my favorite kind of weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever</title>
      <link>/poems/old/whatever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/whatever/</guid>
      <description>2:27, The time without time. Seconds pass slowly, Minutes are stuck forever And Hours don&amp;rsquo;t exist. What I am now Is what I used to be Before I became this whirling vortex Of vain existence and the same sorrows Ever persistent. I fumble with the sheets To no avail, Sleep doesn&amp;rsquo;t come easy to me Not at night, at least. When in doing my chores It comes sudden And treats me like a whore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When_a_tree_dies</title>
      <link>/poems/old/when_a_tree_dies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/when_a_tree_dies/</guid>
      <description>When a tree dies
The wayward souls lose their shade.
Their shade is no more, Neither is the cold whistling of the wind Which moves the leaves A lullaby to listening ears
Listening ears still long for it The rustling leaves, chirping birds, The support to lay their back on All gone when a tree dies
When a tree dies
His son takes up the role. He&amp;rsquo;s not supposed to cry, Or mourn, or show weakness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrote_for_you</title>
      <link>/poems/old/wrote_for_you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/wrote_for_you/</guid>
      <description>I wrote for you. Wasted a thousand words, Filled up a million notes for you.
I showed you my work, I bared what was left of me Broke my mind penning it down, Just to feel that hit of ecstacy.
I poured my heart out. Cliché? I know. Rephrase. I put my soul out and let it wander The white sea of my pages. I let it write free of judgement Beautiful, broken, repugnant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>काला_चश्मा</title>
      <link>/poems/old/%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE_%E0%A4%9A%E0%A4%B6%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/old/%E0%A4%95%E0%A4%BE%E0%A4%B2%E0%A4%BE_%E0%A4%9A%E0%A4%B6%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%AE%E0%A4%BE/</guid>
      <description>भूल जा जो भी तुझे खटक रहा है। जो भी तेरे दिमाग में सांप की तरह भटक चला है। चल आ जी ले ज़िन्दगी को दूसरे नज़रिये से, लगा खुदगर्ज़ी का काला चश्मा। फिर देख जो तेरे दोस्त है वो खुद के नशे में मदहोश है। कोई और नहीं है तेरा तेरे मा बाबा के अलावा। जो भी समजता था तू की सच है भ्रम है वो सब। लगा खुदगर्ज़ी का काला चश्मा और देख ना कोई अपना, ना कोई पराया जिन्होंने तुझे आगे बढ़ाया उसमे उनका भी कोई मतलब था जो भी तुझे लगा प्यार है जुठ, छल, भ्रम, वो सब था।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of a tree</title>
      <link>/poems/death_of_a_tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/death_of_a_tree/</guid>
      <description>When a tree dies
The wayward souls lose their shade.
Their shade is no more, Neither is the cold whistling of the wind which moves the leaves- A lullaby to listening ears
Listening ears still long for it the rustling leaves and chirping birds. The support to lay their back on- All gone when a tree dies.
When a tree dies
His son takes up the role. He&amp;rsquo;s not supposed to cry, or mourn, or show weakness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mangoes in cardboard boxes</title>
      <link>/poems/mangoes_in_cardboard_boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/mangoes_in_cardboard_boxes/</guid>
      <description>like alcohol in the stone pits hailed, wanted, but lonely. In limbo, unhinged from reality thinking about the skies, while baffled by morality.
I scoured the universe, in search of salvation while my god&amp;rsquo;s abode was in my soul&amp;rsquo;s foundation.
like mangoes in cardboard boxes sweet, free from paradoxes In heaven, hinged to reality thinking about the world unbothered by mortality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>अंतर</title>
      <link>/poems/antar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/antar/</guid>
      <description>उदासी तुझमें है, तनहाई मेरे भी अंदर है, लोग वही है, समय बस अलग है। काल चक्र का कोई जादू सा मंतर है। कैसे बताऊं मै? कोई अदृश्य अक्षर है। बातें वही है, बस शब्दों में कुछ अंतर है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Fry</title>
      <link>/poems/smallfry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poems/smallfry/</guid>
      <description>Universes die. Then what am I? A measly human, a small fry.
Life gives and life takes. And the rest of it, death rakes. Civilizations are devoured, Myths forgotten, Languages are lost In the jaws of time.
No one remembers Past two generations Great grandfathers: not so great anymore.
Universes die. Then what am I? A measly human, a small fry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
